'센트럴 퍼크'
우리 중 누가
다음에 결혼할까?
Out of all of us, who do you think
will get married next?
아마도 모니카랑 챈들러
Probably Monica and Chandler.
담배 한 갑 주세요
Could I have a pack of Newport Lights?
여기선 안 팔고
길 건너편에 가면 있어요
We don't sell cigarettes,
but they do across the street.
사다 주실거죠?
고마워요
That'd be great. Thanks.
멜리사 월버트
반겨주기엔 힘이 모자란대
Melissa Worbert. I don't think
I have the energy for this.
맙소사!
레이-레이 그린?
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Greene?
잘 지냈니?!
학교 여학생 클럽의
사보에서 일 했었잖아
You've been MlA
for seven sorority newsletters.
잘 지냈어?
What's up with you?
우리 저쪽에서 얘기할까?
Why don't I tell you over here?
지난번에
너 결혼할거라고 들었는데...
So last I heard
you were gonna get married.
불쌍한 레이-레이
Poor Ray-Ray.
오, 아니야
모든 게 좋아
Oh, no. It's all good.
- 난 랄프 로렌에서 일해
- 거짓말!
-I actually work at Ralph Lauren.
-Shut up!
진짜야, 남자 스포츠복
매장 관리부서야
I will not. I'm the divisional head
of men's sportswear.
잘났어, 얘!
랄프랑도 친하구?
Shut up more!
Are you friends with Ralph?
- 오, 그러지마
- 그래?
-Oh, please.
-Are you?
No.
아니
저녁 한번 먹자
내일 뭐해?
We have to have dinner.
What are you doing tomorrow?
- 내일, 모르겠어
- 이젠 알지, 나랑 저녁 먹잖아
-Tomorrow. I don't know.
-You're having dinner with me.
알았어
Shut up.
가야겠다
반가웠어
I've gotta go.
This has been so great.
Oh, there you are.
왔군요
So listen, just call me.
Here's my card.
- 전화해, 내 명함이야
- 와, 고마워
-You're in real estate?
-No, that's an old card.
- 부동산에서 일해?
- 아니, 옛날거야
I got out of that to do something
where I could...
다른 일 하려고 나왔어
사람들이 변할 수 있게
도와주는 그런 일
help people and make a difference.
What do you do now?
지금은 뭐해?
파티 기획자야
I'm a party planner.
- 내일 보자
- 그래
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
Look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
누가 왔나 봐라
레이-레이야
내 대학친구, 멜리사야
That was my friend, Melissa,
from college.
진짜 재미있는 것 같다!
She seems really, really fun!
진짜 착하고
무지하게 친했지
She's actually sweet,
and we used to be very close.
잠깐만
설마 쟤가 그...?
Wait a minute.
She's not the one who you...?
Who you what? Who you what?
얘가 뭐? 뭐냐니까?
- 그래
- 우와!
-Yes.
-Wow!
우와, 뭐?
진짜 뭐냐니까?
Wow, what? Who you what?
오, 별거 아냐
Oh, it's not a big deal.
연인사이였어
They were lovers.
- 뭐?
- 진짜야?
-What?
아니야
아무 것도 아니었어
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
4학년때, 어느날 밤
파티에서
It was one night, senior year,
and we went to a party...
술을 진짜 많이 마셨거든
그리고 결국에는
had a lot of sangria,
and you know, ended up...
kissing for a bit.
살짝 뽀뽀했거든
아내중 둘이나 게이네
So that's two of my wives.
The One With Rachel's Big Kiss
So this is where the band is.
And here's the bar.
밴드는 여기 있을거고
바는 여기고
And all these pins have people's names
on them. Rach, here you are.
핀에는 이름이 적혀있어
레이첼, 넌 여기
Why don't we just put me
with a Manhattan in my hand...
그냥 손님들 사이에 넣어줘
talking to the cute bartender.
괜찮은 사람 있으면 꼬시게
These pins aren't for playing,
are they?
이걸로 장난치면 안되지,
그치?
The red are my guests,
and the blue are yours.
빨간색은 내 손님,
파란색은 자기 손님
This is so sad.
I only have like 10 pins.
너무 슬프다
내 손님은 10명 밖에 안되네
Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
챈들러, 괜찮아
경쟁도 아닌데 뭐
Certainly not a close one.
그랬으면 가망도 없었겠지
Hey, Rach.
안녕, 레이첼
Stop picturing it!
상상하지마!
I think that's it. The seating chart
is done. This is our wedding.
다된 것 같아, 하객자리는 다됐어
멋진 결혼식이 되겠지
They all look like they're having fun.
모두가 즐거워 보인다
그치?
So where are my parents gonna be?
우리 부모님 자리는 어디야?
보자, 여기가 웨딩 홀이면
Well, if this is the wedding hall...
your parents would be over here
at home in Queens.
퀸스에 있는 집에 계시겠지
They're not invited?
Oh, no, they're gonna be crushed!
초대 안 하는 거야?
안 돼, 섭섭해 하실 텐데!
Why would they think they're invited?
왜 초대해야 하는데?
You got me. I don't...
글쎄, 뭐 잘은...
-Joey!
-Look, I thought parents were coming.
- 조이!
- 부모님들도 오시는 줄 알았지
Your parents are coming.
Chandler's are coming.
너희 부모님 오시잖아
챈들러 부모님도
Ross' parents are coming.
로스 부모님도 오시고
Ross' parents are my parents.
로스 부모님이
우리 부모님이야
Well, see, parents are coming.
봐, 부모님들이 오시잖아
-We should invite them.
-You just want more blue pins.
- 초대해야 돼
- 파란 핀을 더 원하는 거겠지
Well, this is just sad.
이건 너무 비참하잖아
All right. Maybe I can fit them in
if I just do some rearranging.
좋아, 조금만
다시 배치하면 될거야
Rachel may have to sit at the bar.
레이첼은 바에 앉아야 해
That is not a problem.
문제없지
-Maybe you'll order a little sangria.
-Get out of here!
- 아마 샹그리아를 주문할거고
- 이걸 진짜!
These are our tuxedos. If you like
anything, we can make a deal.
우리 예복이야, 맘에 드는거
있으면 여기서 해
Anything at all. But these are
the three that Monica pre-approved.
아무거나, 근데 요 세벌이
모니카가 골라 논거지
Thanks a lot for hooking me up.
신경써 줘서 고맙네
And I want you to know that I want
you to attend our wedding as my guest.
결혼식에 내 게스트로
참석해 줬으면 하는데
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
난 모니카의 들러리라구
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
신랑측으로 꼬실 생각 마
-Well, these look nice.
-They are nice.
- 음, 이것들 멋있네
- 물론이지
When celebrities are done with them,
they send them back.
유명인들은 식이 끝나면
이 옷들을 반납하거든
-You mean like for award shows?
-Some of them.
- 시상식처럼?
- 다는 아니고
빨간색 카페트위에 서 있으면
사람들이
They've been down the red carpet
with people yelling...
'누가 디자인 한 거예요?
멋져요!'
"Who are you wearing?
You look fabulous!"
Might I suggest watching
a little more ESPN...
스포트 채널 좀
더 보도록 해
연예채널은 줄이고!
and a little less E!.
Okay. Who wore those?
알았어
누가 입던거야?
-Well, this one's Tom Brokaw.
-Not bad.
- 이건 탐 브로코
- 괜찮네
This one is Paul O'Neill.
이건 폴 오닐
Who's that?
그게 누군데?
He plays for the Yankees.
Seriously, ESPN.
양키팀 소속,
진짜 스포츠 채널 좀 더 봐
Just once in a while.
Have it on in the background.
가끔 가다가
뒷배경으로 틀어봐
-This one was Pierce Brosnan.
-Pierce Brosnan?
- 피어스 브로스넌이 입던거야
- 피어스 브로스넌?
Are you serious?
진짜야?
007?
This is James Bond's tux? I have to
get married in James Bond's tux.
제임스 본드가 입던 턱시도?
나 이거 입고 결혼할래
It's a pretty cool tux.
진짜 멋지군
It's not just that. I would be
England's most powerful weapon.
그뿐이 아냐, 영국최고의
강력한 무기도 있잖아
A jet-setting heartbreaker
on Her Majesty's secret service.
비밀 요원을 실어 나르는
초고속 제트도 있고
A man who fears no one,
with a license to kill.
살인 면허를 소지한
아무것도 두렵지 않은 사람
Would Monica let me wear this?
모니카가 입으라고 할까?
We should really learn
how to play the real way.
진짜로 하는 방식도
배워야 할거다
I like our way.
난 이 방식이 좋아
Chess!
체스!
-Nice move.
-Yeah.
- 좀 하네
- 그 정도야
I hooked Ross and Chandler up
with tuxedos. Do you need one?
로스랑 챈들러 턱시도 골라 줬는데
너도 필요해?
No, I'm not wearing a tux.
난 턱시도 안 입어
-What are you gonna wear?
-Multi-colored robes.
- 뭐 입을 건데?
- 여러색깔 들어간 가운
And maybe a hat.
모자도 쓰고
-Does Monica know about this?
-No.
- 모니카도 알아?
- 아니
Can I please be there
when you tell her?
너 그런 얘기할 때
거기 있어도 될까?
You want to go to a movie tonight?
오늘밤에 영화 보러 갈래?
I'm having dinner with Melissa.
멜리사랑 저녁 약속있어
Can I come?
나 가도 돼?
I won't talk.
You'll just hear my video camera.
아무 말 안 할께
캠코더로만 찍을께
-What? What's going on?
-Can I tell her?
- 뭐? 무슨 일인데?
- 얘기해도 돼?
Do you want what happened,
or Joey's lewd version?
진실을 원해, 조이 식의
추잡한 얘기를 원해?
- 조이 식
- 알았어
Joey's.
I had this college friend...
내 대학 동창인데
and I made the mistake
of telling Joey that one time...
조이한테 그걸 얘기한게
큰 실수지
she and I, you know,
kissed a little bit.
걔랑 내가, 저기...
살짝 키스했거든
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
그래, 그럴 수도 있지
-It did.
-Sure.
- 그랬어
- 그랬겠지
Hey. It happened.
아니, 진짜로 그랬다고
It was senior year.
It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
4학년때 였어
장학생들 파티가 끝나구
and Melissa and I got very drunk.
멜리사랑 난
술이 많이 취했었거든
And we ended up kissing.
For several minutes.
결국 키스까지 했지
몇 분 동안
Which means she had a couple spritzers
and a peck on the cheek.
와인에 소다 섞어서 두어 잔 마시고
볼에다 좀 한거겠지
Why are you taking this away from me?
왜 자꾸 딴 소리야?
Why is it so hard for you to believe?
왜 못 믿니?
Okay. I just didn't know
that you were a lesbian.
알았어
니가 레즈비언인지 몰랐어
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian.
I'm just saying that this happened.
레즈비언이라고 말하는 게 아냐
그런일이 있었다는 얘기지
It just seems pretty wild.
And you're so...
믿기 힘들어
그러면 넌...
vanilla.
참 밋밋하다
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla.
I do lots of crazy things.
밋밋? 무슨 소리야?
내가 얼마나 웃기는데
I mean, I got drunk
and married in Vegas.
술 마시고
라스베가스에서 결혼했잖아
To Ross.
로스랑
If you don't believe me...
나 못 믿겠으면
just come with me to dinner tonight
and she'll tell you.
나랑 같이가
내 친구가 얘기해 줄 거야
Okay. Because I can't picture it.
좋아, 상상할 수가 없거든
You should get inside my head.
내 머리 속을 들여다봐라
결혼식에 어떻게 하고 갈지
맞춰봐
Guess what I got for your wedding?
기이하고 엽기적으로?
A freakishly thin date
with a hanger for a head?
Rachel hooked me up with a tux.
But not just any tux.
레이첼이 턱시도 골라줬는데
평범한 게 아니야
Batman's tux!
배트맨 턱시도지!
-What?
-That's right.
- 뭐?
- 그래
Made expressly for Val Kilmer,
and worn by him in the hit film...
발 킬머가 배트맨에서
멋지게 입은거라구
that Batman film he was in.
그가 나온 배트맨 말야
입지 마
나도 유명한거 입을 거거든
You can't wear that.
I'm wearing the famous tux.
- 제임스 본드꺼!
- 근데?
If you wear that,
it'll make mine less special.
근데 라니? 니가 그걸 입으면
내 옷이 덜 빛나잖아
You need something to
to make it special?
니가 날 좀 특별하게
만들어 줘야지
You have
the most special thing of all.
이봐!
최고로 특별한게 있잖아
니가 사랑하는 사람이랑
결혼 하는거
You are marrying the woman you love.
Don't take away my cool thing.
Pretty please?
날 좀 부각되게 해야할 거 아냐
부탁이다
"Pretty please?" Not very 007.
'부탁이다'?
007 답지 않군
If you were getting married,
I'd never do anything to upset you.
이게 네 결혼이라면
난 너 화나게 안 했을거다
-You slept with my sister.
-That was pretty 007.
- 내 동생이랑 잤잖아?
- 그건 007 같네
좋아, 여기 있어
내가 해결했어
All right, I figured it out.
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8,
add your parents...
8개 중에서 테이블 둘을 빼서
너희 부모님을
and make them into 3 tables of 6.
추가해서 6개 중
3개를 만드는 거야
And I called the caterer.
We are good to go!
요리사한테 전화했어
준비 끝!
Yeah. They're not coming.
안 오실거야
What?
뭐?
They think that you only
invited them because of me.
나 때문에 초대됐다고
생각하시니까
They feel unwanted.
불청객 같으신거야
That's too bad.
It's true. But too bad.
어머나,
사실이긴 하지만 안됐다
If you could just call my mom.
우리 엄마께 전화해서
참석하시길 바란다고
말씀드려
Just let her know
you want them there.
This is a woman
who has sent you many lasagnas.
우리 엄마가 이태리 음식도
많이 보내 주셨잖아
No, she hasn't.
아닌것 같은데
Is it her fault
if some didn't make it to you?
배달 안된게 엄마 잘못이냐?
What am I gonna say?
뭐라고 말씀드리지?
Tell them you mixed up invitations.
No, blame it on the post office.
초대장이 섞였었다고 해
아니, 우체부가 잘못 했다고 그래
They hate the post office.
And the Irish.
우체부 싫어하셔
그리고 아일랜드 사람도
But I don't think
you could blame it on them.
그러면 안 될 것 같은데
Hello? Yeah, hi. Mrs. Tribbianni?
This is Monica Geller.
안녕하세요, 트리비아니
부인이시죠? 모니카 겔러예요
I'm just calling to say that I really
hope you can make the wedding.
결혼식에 꼭 오셨으면 해서
전화드립니다
Apparently some of our invitations
weren't delivered.
초대장들이
잘 배달이 안 되나봐요
I guess there was some screw-up
at the damn post office.
어리버리한
우체부들이 있나봐요
Tell me about it!
맞아요!
Yeah, the U.S. Post Office?
No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
우체국이 아니라
'우째그러노' 인가봐요
What are they, Irish?
아일랜드 사람들 아녜요?
Anyway, his name's Allen. And we've
been going out for three years.
어쨌든, 엘랜이고
3년동안 사귀었어
He was my first client
when I became a party planner.
파티 기획자가 됐을때
내 첫 고객이었거든
그때 자기 여자친구를 위한
파티를 준비했었어
He was actually planning a party
for his girlfriend at the time.
그랬어
Oh, well.
-He was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse.
-That's great.
- 시라큐스 대학의 장학생이었거든
- 멋지네
-Were you ever in a sorority?
-Of course.
- 피비, 여학생 클럽에 있었니?
- 물론
Yes. I was a Thigh Mega Tampon.
거 뭐시기 클럽에 있었어
What one?
뭐라구?
We were huge too.
But they had to shut us down...
우리도 꽤 컸는데
결국 해체 됐어
when Regina Phalangie
died of alcohol poisoning.
레지나 팔란지가
알코올 중독으로 죽었거든
Isn't it a shame when one girl
ruins it for the whole bunch?
한사람으로 인해서 조직이
망가지는건 질색이야
Anyway...
어쨌든...
Speaking of drinking too much,
I told Phoebe...
술 하면 생각 나는게 있지
피비한테 말 했거든
about that crazy night after the
Sigma Chi luau where we made out.
그때 파티 끝나고
우리 그랬던 날
What?
뭐?
Remember we.. Come on, we had sarongs
on and the coconut bikini tops.
기억나? 왜 허리에 뭐 감고
코코넛 뚜껑으로 가슴 가렸던거
We went back to the house
and got really silly...
그리고 집으로 돌아가서
약간 미친 것 처럼
and we made out.
그거 했었잖아
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
와, 레이-레이
무슨 얘길 하는지 모르겠다
Really?
정말?
로스가 배트맨꺼 입는데
Ross is Batman.
Well, he did manage to keep
his identity secret for a long time.
자기 신분을
오래도 숨겨왔네
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo
that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
레이첼이 발 킬머가 배트맨에서
입었던 옷을 로스에게 줬다구
배트맨이 제임스 본드보다
훨씬 멋져
Batman is so much cooler
than James Bond.
- 007은 모든 도구들이 다 있잖아
- 배트맨은 만능 벨트가 있어
-What? 007 has all those gadgets.
-Batman has a utility belt.
- 007은 멋진 차있어
- 배트맨은 배트맨 차 있잖아
-007 has a fancy car.
-Batman has the Batmobile.
- 007은 여자들이 많아
- 배트맨한테는 로빈이 있어
-007 gets all the ladies.
-Batman has Robin.
We get ESPN, right?
우리 스포츠 채널 나오지?
007 턱시도 한번 입어봐
내가 마티니 만들어 줄께
How about you go put on your 007
tuxedo, and I'll make you a martini?
난 마티니 별론데
I don't like martinis.
- 초코우유에 빨대 꽂아 줄까?
- 맛있겠다
-A Yoo-Hoo with a funny straw?
-Yum.
초대장에
오후 6시로 돼있는데
I know the invitation says 6 p.m.
6시까지 도착하라는 거야
6시에 쇼가 시작한다는 거야?
But does that mean get there at 6,
or the show starts at 6?
'쇼'라구?
The show?
그래, 결혼식, 미안
Right, the wedding. Gotcha.
결혼식은 조금 늦게
시작하겠지, 그치?
But weddings start
a little late, right?
Have you ever
been to one of my weddings?
내 결혼식에 와 본 적 있니?
내 조카의 세례식하고
날짜가 겹치는데
Well, it's the same day
as my niece's christening...
거기서 부모님이
날 보셨으면 해서
and I want my parents to see me.
난 주로 시작 부분에 나오잖냐?
그 쇼에...결혼식에
My part's in the beginning. I'm not
in the rest of the show.. Wedding.
The wedding starts at 6.
결혼식은 6시에 시작해
그래, 알았어
Okay. I totally hear you.
이건 어때?
오실 때까지 바람잡이를 할게
How about this?
I vamp till they get there.
'바람잡이'?
You'll "vamp"?
손님들 좀 챙긴다고
어디서 오셨는지도 물어보고
Like warm up the crowd.
Ask where they're from.
In Joey Tribbiani, you get
a minister and an entertainer.
주례와 접대를 동시에 할 수 있는
조이 트리비아니가 있으니까
'주접'이라고 불러줘
I'm a "ministainer."
누구도 따라 올 수 없는
유일한 남자
There's no one better.
There's no one greater.
어떻게 키스한 걸
잊을 수가 있어?
How can you not remember us kissing?
모르겠어, 없던 일들은
전혀 기억이 안나네
I don't know. I don't remember
a lot of things that never happened.
기억해봐, 소파 위에서
계속 낄낄거렸잖아
Remember, we were on the sleeping
porch? We couldn't stop giggling.
코코넛은 우리 사이에서
부딪히고
Our coconuts kept knocking together.
조이가 들었으면 좋아했겠다
Somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
불편하게 만들고 싶지 않지만
I don't want
to make you uncomfortable...
피비한테 이 얘길 했는데
내 말을 안 믿잖아
but I told Phoebe it happened,
and she doesn't believe me.
미안해, 그런일이 있었다면
그렇다고 하지
I'm sorry. I mean, if I thought
it happened, I would say it.
내가 술 먹고 자는 동안
니가 그렇게 했나?
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff
to me while I was sleeping.
아니야!
It's okay, you don't have to do this.
I believe you.
괜찮아, 이럴 필요 없어
널 믿어
If you say you kissed Melissa,
then you kissed Melissa.
니가 멜리사랑
키스했다고 하면 한 거야
-Thank you, Phoebe.
-Okay.
- 고마워, 피비
- 그래
-But she didn't.
-I know.
- 안 했어
- 알아
계속 가지고 다니는 거야?
You carry that around?
응, 이게 얘깃거리가
되더라구
I find it to be something
of a conversation piece.
- 오빠랑..?
- 건더
-Between you and...?
-Gunther.
Why don't we put them on?
같이 입어 보자
배트맨하고 제임스 본드처럼
Get a picture of Batman
and James Bond, together.
그래,
근데 바지가 약간 낀다
I would, but my pants
are a little tight.
약간 껴? 00 하고 7 이
그 사이에 보인다
A little tight?
I could see 00 and 7 in those things.
뭐야, 임마
I was looking forward to wearing
our celebrity tuxes together.
유명인사의 턱시도를
같이 입고 싶었는데
- 니꺼 안 입을거야?
- 농담해? 배트맨 턱시도야!
-So you're not gonna be wearing yours?
- Are you kidding? It's Batman's tux!
내가 입어볼께
Let me try it on.
좋아, 자켓만 입어봐
00 사이에 7 있는데는 안 돼
Okay. But just the jacket.
00 and 7 are not getting in there.
죽이게 편하다, 배트맨아!
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
이게 뭐야?
What's this?
첫 번째 만남의 초대장?
An invitation to
the At First Sight premiere?
발 킬머는 배트맨에서
이거 안 입어
Val Kilmer didn't
wear this in Batman.
달콤한 사랑 장면에서
장님으로 나올 때 입은거라구
He wore it to the premiere of a fruity
love story where he was a blind guy.
어디 좀 보자
Let me see that.
Oh, man.
맙소사
The only super power you have is the
slightly heightened sense of smell.
니가 바라던 그 배트맨의
초능력은 가질 수가 없겠다
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
잠깐 얘기 좀 할래?
I give up.
Whatever you want, you can have it.
그래, 졌다
니가 하고 싶은데로해
노래부르거나 춤추길 원해?
You want to sing a song or do a dance?
어머님이 오셔서 뭐라고
하시던간 상관 안 해
You want your mom at the altar
screaming racial slurs? I don't care.
I just want to thank you guys
for what you did for my parents.
그냥 우리 부모님 초대해줘서
고맙다고 말하려던 건데
They're so happy
to be a part of your special day.
특별한 날에 초대되셔서
두 분다 기쁘시데
Tell them we're glad they're coming.
참석해 주신다니
감사하다고 말씀드려
I will. Oh, check out what they got
me to wear for the ceremony!
그래, 식장에서 쓰라고
뭘 보내 주셨나 봐라!
I wear it like this when I
marry you guys. And then this...
주례 할 때는 이렇게 쓰고
그리고
is for party time.
파티 할 땐 이렇게...
그랬다니까
분명히 그랬다고
It happened.
I am telling you it happened.
만나서 반가웠어
It was great meeting you.
레이첼? 그리고
이젠 다신 보지말자
And, Rachel? I don't think
I'll be calling you because...
너 좀 이상해 진 것 같아
you know, you've gotten weird.
잘 지내라, 둘다
Take care, you guys.
아니, 잠깐만
Wait a minute. Okay, look.
그날 그랬던 건 정말 내 인생에서
처음 있는 일이었다구
That night was the one wild thing
I've ever done in my life.
그냥 이런 식으로 보낼 순 없어
I won't let you take it away.
그건 기억 못하더라도
이건 기억 할거다
So if you don't remember that,
maybe you'll remember this...
맙소사
나 사랑하는구나
Oh, my God. You love me.
What?
뭐?
Of course I remember.
I think about it all the time.
물론 기억하지
어떻게 잊을 수가 있겠니
I can still hear
the coconuts knocking together...
아직 그 코코넛 부딪히는
소리도 들리고...
I didn't want to tell you, because I
didn't think you'd return my love...
니가 돌아오지 않을까 봐
말을 안 한거야
Look who's being suddenly shy.
부끄러워 하지마
You have to feel what I feel.
그냥 내가 느끼는 대로 느껴
Nobody can kiss that good
and not mean it.
아무도 너 만큼 키스를 못해
I'm just a good kisser.
그냥 키스를
잘 하는 것 뿐이야
Shut up.
잘났다
I'm sorry.
미안
You don't have to be sorry.
미안해 할 필요없어
I'm obviously kidding.
장난이니까
I'm not in love with you.
I'm not in love with her.
사랑에 빠진 건 아냐
저 친구한테도 아니고
I don't hear coconuts
banging together.
코코넛 부딪히는 소리는
무슨...
I don't picture your face
when I make love to my boyfriend.
남자친구랑 사랑할 때
니 생각 안났고
Anyway, I gotta go.
어쨌든, 가야겠다
A kiss goodbye?
작별키스는?
No? Okay.
싫어? 알았어
I mean, I had no idea
that that would...
난 도대체 뭐가 뭔지...
What the hell was that?
뭐하는 짓이야?
Just wanted to see
what all the fuss was about.
그냥 그런게 어떤건지
알고 싶어서
-And?
-I've had better.
- 그래서?
- 그럭저럭
맞는거 찾았어
I found one that fits.
그게 벌써 23번째다
그거 아니?
Well, you know what they say?
23rd time's a charm.
어머, 잘 어울리는데
Look at you, all handsome.
- 누가 입었었어?
- 상관 있어?
-Whose is it?
-Does it matter?
니가 입어서 멋있으면 되지
All that matters
is that you look so handsome.
- 누가 입었었어?
- 말 안 할래
-Whose is it?
-I don't want to say.
괜찮아, 괜찮다니까
누가 입었었냐니까?
Come on, I don't care. Whose is it?
여배우가...
Diane Keaton.